







ITIL Lead Consultant seeking roles in IT Project Management, Business Analysis, Risk Management, Stakeholder Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Process Automation, Agile Methodology, Net, SQL

Server, JavaScript, HTML, Oracle, Java

Current Designation: Lead Consultant -IT Total Experience: 13 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Virtusa Consulting Services Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E.

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Business Analyst

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Lead Consultant, Business Analyst, IT Project Management, Business Analysis, Risk Management, Stakeholder Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Process Automation, Agile

Methodology

Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

# Summary

Aresult-oriented professional with nearly 13 years of experience in Business Analysis across Telecom & Media-Ad Sales domains

Rendered assistance in leading product development from an E2E perspective

Maintained close coordination with client subject matter experts and technical organization by planning, conducting and completing analysis of highly complex business problems to be solved with automated systems

Rich onsite & offsite experience in design, development, testing and implementation of applications for various clients Designed, tracked, interpreted, and modified reports, metrics, and analytical models that support campaign performance, media efficiencies and sales growth

Collaborated with business partners to identify opportunities to apply new insights to various areas of the organization i.e. Business Intelligence, Sales, Marketing Communications

## **Work Experience**

- Virtusa Consulting Services as Lead Consultant -IT Feb 2017 to Till Date
- iOpex Technologies as Service Design Architect Dec 2016 to Feb 2017
- Magnaquest Technologies as Solution Architect Dec 2014 to Dec 2016

^ Back to Top

# Education

 $\hbox{ UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Hectronics/Telecommunication) from SMK FOMRA institute of technology, anna university in 2005. A property of the propert$ 

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

ITIL Foundation Certification

^ Back to Top

### IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

# **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

.NET		-
SQL SERVER 2014		
JavaScript		
HTML		
ORACLE 12C		
JAVA		

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Proficient	✓		✓
Telugu	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Tamil	Beginner			✓

^ Back to Top

### **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.